I don't care what you guys say Harry and
the Hendersons is legit no we said it
was legit yeah there's my birthday
present that I got you oh dude put in BO
thanks so much except you're lying I had
this next a last night oh that's a
chop who wants to do a snippet I love
Snippets uh actually wait they're
whippets right yeah it's whipp it people
call them Snippets now what if we just
uh ducked out into the bathroom and got
drunk like usual that'd be fun no we are
making memories and then destroying
them okay no that is hippie crack man
did we not all cry during that steo
documentary relax your mind I'm going to
blast
off
oh we're just celebrating big dur dog's
birthday yeah because the dur dog and
then there's everything that's happens
to sorry nothing yeah he's monkeying
around again whatever look uh there's a
big surprise for you in the break room
it's a birthday cake anyway I'm not
going okay Anders we have a dress code
can you
please it's Greg Norman